CHANCE CUSACK

TECHNICAL LEAD

PROFILE

Born and raised in New Jersey, I've traveled the world and worked in numerous design and technology fields, both on site and remote. I majored in Creative Arts and Technology, received a BA in Game Development and published numerous titles. I have been the sole post-production manager for a successful photography studio, helped start one business as well as revive many others. I currently spend my days ensuring bp is technologically ready for the future.

I am able to do this by providing only the best in service and support by applying an evolving set of skills and best-practices learned over two decades of hands-on experience.

EDUCATION

BA / Creative Arts & Technology Bloomfield College | 2007 - 2011

Focused on Game Development which provided ground-level access to industry-standard design and development tools, programs, and the application thereof.

Digital Media Production AUCB / 2009-2010

Study abroad semester in Bournemouth, UK. Was taught hands-on digital design skills and techniques, led by industry leaders.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL LEAD, myIT bar @ bp

HCL Technologies | September 2019 - Present

- Serve as technical lead in a tier 3 capacity to oversee daily ops and handle complex escalations as virtual and physical walk-up support point of contact
- Connect with service owners to inform, address and resolve major issues affecting local/global systems
- Lead and manage team of over 40 global techs
- Assist in training of new virtual/remote support agents
- · Assist in development, testing, and maintenance of internal applications and tools
- Draft documentation supporting new applications and workflows
- · Track trending issues and metrics with internal analytics

DESKTOP SUPPORT ENGINEER, myIT bar @ bp

Prosource.it | March 2018 - September 2019

- · Provided hands-on support and resolved issues affecting computers, mobile
- devices and various other system/server configs for dozens of end-users per day
- Performed daily issue and resolution tracking through internal ticketing systems
- Trained users in modern technology best-practices

WEB ADVISOR

Endurance International Group | Feb 2017 - Jan 2018

- · Front-line support handling incoming requests for web hosting related technical issues
- Provided hosting solutions and support for 15,000+ global users
- Solution delivery ranged from client-side programming and design conflicts to serverside compatibility failures
- Absorbed sales responsibility and have exceeded \$30,000 in direct company profit

OWNER | DESIGN / IT GENERALIST

Project{Radial} | 2011 - Present

Providing tech, design, and IT services. Work includes logo/graphic/web design and development, hands-on hardware/software troubleshooting, as well as emergency repair and support services. Recent clients include:

- · Grace Mercy Love GSD Rescue: Web/graphic designer
- Val's Pals GSD Rescue: Web/graphic designer
- Ron Mafrige Enterprises: Graphic designer
- Olga Gagne Realty: Web/graphic designer
- MacKenzie Management Solutions: Web/graphic designer
- CK2 Consulting: Web/design/IT consultant

SKILLS

Adobe CS Windows/OSX Linux/Bash HTML/CSS/JS PHP/MySQL Web Design Azure/O365 Break/Fix AWS



CONTACT

Houston, TX 77077

t: 732.239.5410

e: chance.cusack@gmail.com

w: projectradial.com

w: chancecusack.com